A Guide to the Annual Tax and Operation Reports for Railroads, 1899-1975
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Annual Tax and Operation Reports for Railroads, 1899-1975., Extent: 366 boxes; 165 cubic feet. (Box 1-366)
  - 1948.
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1948 (Box 282)
    - Pennsylvania, 1948 (Box 282)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1948 (Box 282)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1948 (Box 282)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1948 (Box 282)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1948 (Box 283)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1948 (Box 283)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1948 (Box 283)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1948 (Box 283)
    - Smithfield Terminal, 1948 (Box 283)
    - Southern, 1948 (Box 283)
    - Swords Creek, 1948 (Box 283)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1948 (Box 283)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1948 (Box 283)
    - Virginia Central, 1948 (Box 283)
    - Virginian, 1948 (Box 284)
    - Virginia Transit, 1948 (Box 284)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1948 (Box 284)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1948 (Box 284)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1948 (Box 284)
    - Winchester and Western, 1948 (Box 284)
  - 1949.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1949 (Box 284)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1949 (Box 284)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1949 (Box 285)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1949 (Box 285)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1949 (Box 285)
    - Clinchfield, 1949 (Box 285)
    - Coverdale and Catawba, 1949 (Box 285)
    - Danville and Western, 1949 (Box 285)
    - Franklin and Carolina, 1949 (Box 285)
    - Interstate, 1949 (Box 285)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1949 (Box 285)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1949 (Box 286)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1949 (Box 286)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1949 (Box 286)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1949 (Box 286)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1949 (Box 286)
    - Pennsylvania, 1949 (Box 286)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1949 (Box 286)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac 1949 (Box 287)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1949 (Box 287)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1949 (Box 287)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1949 (Box 287)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1949 (Box 287)
    - Smithfield Terminal, 1949 (Box 287)
    - Southern, 1949 (Box 287)
    - Swords Creek, 1949 (Box 287)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1949 (Box 288)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1949 (Box 288)
    - Virginia Central, 1949 (Box 288)
    - Virginian, 1949 (Box 288)
    - Virginia Transit Company, 1949 (Box 288)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1949 (Box 288)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1949 (Box 288)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1949 (Box 288)
    - Winchester and Western, 1949 (Box 288)
  - 1950.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1950 (Box 288)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1950 (Box 288)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1950 (Box 289)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1950 (Box 289)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1950 (Box 289)
    - Clinchfield, 1950 (Box 289)
    - Cloverdale and Catawba, 1950 (Box 289)
    - Danville and Western, 1950 (Box 289)
    - Franklin and Western, 1950 (Box 289)
    - Interstate, 1950 (Box 289)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1950 (Box 290)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1950 (Box 290)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1950 (Box 290)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1950 (Box 290)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1950 (Box 290)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1950 (Box 290)
    - Pennsylvania, 1950 (Box 290)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated, 1950 (Box 290)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated, 1950 (Box 291)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1950 (Box 291)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1950 (Box 291)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1950 (Box 291)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1950 (Box 291)
    - Southern, 1950 (Box 291)
    - Swords Creek, 1950 (Box 291)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1950 (Box 291)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1950 (Box 292)
    - Virginia Central, 1950 (Box 292)
    - Virginian, 1950 (Box 292)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1950 (Box 292)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1950 (Box 292)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1950 (Box 292)
    - Winchester and Western, 1950 (Box 292)
  - 1951.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1951 (Box 292)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1951 (Box 292)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1951 (Box 292)
    - Carolina and Northwestern, 1951 (Box 293)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1951 (Box 293)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1951 (Box 293)
    - Clinchfield, 1951 (Box 293)
    - Danville and Western, 1951 (Box 293)
    - Franklin and Carolina, 1951 (Box 293)
    - Interstate, 1951 (Box 293)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1951 (Box 294)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1951 (Box 294)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1951 (Box 294)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1951 (Box 294)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1951 (Box 294)
    - Pennsylvania, 1951 (Box 294)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1951 (Box 295)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1951 (Box 295)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1951 (Box 295)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1951 (Box 295)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1951 (Box 295)
    - Southern, 1951 (Box 295)
    - Swords Creek, 1951 (Box 295)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1951 (Box 296)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1951 (Box 296)
    - Virginia Central, 1951 (Box 296)
    - Virginian, 1951 (Box 296)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1951 (Box 296)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1951 (Box 296)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1951 (Box 296)
    - Winchester and Western, 1951 (Box 296)
  - 1952.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1952 (Box 296)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1952 (Box 297)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1952 (Box 297)
    - Carolina and Northwestern, 1952 (Box 297)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1952 (Box 297)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1952 (Box 297)
    - Clinchfield, 1952 (Box 297)
    - Danville and Western, 1952 (Box 297)
    - Franklin and Carolina, 1952 (Box 298)
    - Interstate, 1952 (Box 298)
    - Louisville Nashville, 1952 (Box 298)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1952 (Box 298)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1952 (Box 298)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1952 (Box 298)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1952 (Box 298)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1952 (Box 298)
    - Pennsylvania, 1952 (Box 299)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1952 (Box 299)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1952 (Box 299)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1952 (Box 299)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1952 (Box 299)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1952 (Box 299)
    - Southern, 1952 (Box 300)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1952 (Box 300)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1952 (Box 300)
    - Virginia Central, 1952 (Box 300)
    - Virginian, 1952 (Box 300)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1952 (Box 300)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1952 (Box 300)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1952 (Box 300)
    - Winchester and Western, 1952 (Box 300)
  - 1953.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1953 (Box 301)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1953 (Box 301)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1953 (Box 301)
    - Carolina and Northwestern, 1953 (Box 301)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1953 (Box 301)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1953 (Box 301)
    - Clinchfield, 1953 (Box 302)
    - Danville and Western, 1953 (Box 302)
    - Franklin and Carolina, 1953 (Box 302)
    - Interstate, 1953 (Box 302)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1953 (Box 302)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1953 (Box 302)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1953 (Box 302)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1953 (Box 302)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1953 (Box 303)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1953 (Box 303)
    - Pennsylvania, 1953 (Box 303)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1953 (Box 303)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1953 (Box 303)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1953 (Box 303)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1953 (Box 303)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1953 (Box 304)
    - Southern, 1953 (Box 304)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1953 (Box 304)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1953 (Box 304)
    - Virginia Central, 1953 (Box 304)
    - Virginian, 1953 (Box 304)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1953 (Box 304)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1953 (Box 304)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1953 (Box 305)
    - Winchester and Western, 1953 (Box 305)
  - 1954.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1954 (Box 305)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1954 (Box 305)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1954 (Box 305)
    - Carolina and Northwestern, 1954 (Box 305)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1954 (Box 305)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1954 (Box 306)
    - Clinchfield, 1954 (Box 306)
    - Danville and Western, 1954 (Box 306)
    - Franklin and Carolina, 1954 (Box 306)
    - Interstate, 1954 (Box 306)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1954 (Box 306)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1954 (Box 306)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1954 (Box 306)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1954 (Box 307)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1954 (Box 307)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1954 (Box 307)
    - Pennsylvania, 1954 (Box 307)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1954 (Box 307)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1954 (Box 307)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1954 (Box 307)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1954 (Box 308)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1954 (Box 308)
    - Southern, 1954 (Box 308)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1954 (Box 308)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1954 (Box 308)
    - Virginia Central, 1954 (Box 308)
    - Virginian, 1954 (Box 308)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1954 (Box 308)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1954 (Box 309)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1954 (Box 309)
    - Winchester and Western, 1954 (Box 309)
  - 1955.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1955 (Box 309)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1955 (Box 309)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1955 (Box 309)
    - Carolina and Northwestern, 1955 (Box 309)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1955 (Box 309)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1955 (Box 310)
    - Clinchfield, 1955 (Box 310)
    - Danville and Western, 1955 (Box 310)
    - Franklin and Carolina, 1955 (Box 310)
    - Interstate, 1955 (Box 310)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1955 (Box 310)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1955 (Box 310)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1955 (Box 310)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1955 (Box 311)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1955 (Box 311)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1955 (Box 311)
    - Pennsylvania, 1955 (Box 311)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1955 (Box 311)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1955 (Box 311)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1955 (Box 311)
    - Rossyln Connecting, 1955 (Box 312)
    - Seaboard Air Lines, 1955 (Box 312)
    - Southern, 1955 (Box 312)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1955 (Box 312)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1955 (Box 312)
    - Virginia Central, 1955 (Box 312)
    - Virginian, 1955 (Box 312)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1955 (Box 312)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1955 (Box 313)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1955 (Box 313)
    - Winchester and Western, 1955 (Box 313)
  - 1956.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1956 (Box 313)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1956 (Box 313)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1956 (Box 313)
    - Carolina and Northwestern, 1956 (Box 313)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1956 (Box 313)
    - Cheseapeake Western, 1956 (Box 314)
    - Clinchfield, 1956 (Box 314)
    - Danville and Western, 1956 (Box 314)
    - Franklin and Carolina, 1956 (Box 314)
    - Interstate, 1956 (Box 314)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1956 (Box 314)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1956 (Box 314)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1956 (Box 314)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1956 (Box 314)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1956 (Box 314)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1956 (Box 314)
    - Pennsylvania, 1956 (Box 315)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1956 (Box 315)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1956 (Box 315)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1956 (Box 315)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1956 (Box 315)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1956 (Box 315)
    - Southern, 1956 (Box 315)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1956 (Box 316)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1956 (Box 316)
    - Virginia Central, 1956 (Box 316)
    - Virginian, 1956 (Box 316)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1956 (Box 316)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1956 (Box 316)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1956 (Box 316)
    - Winchester and Western, 1956 (Box 316)
  - 1957.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1957 (Box 316)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1957 (Box 316)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1957 (Box 316)
    - Carolina and Northwestern, 1957 (Box 316)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1957 (Box 316)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1957 (Box 317)
    - Clinchfield, 1957 (Box 317)
    - Danville and Western, 1957 (Box 317)
    - Franklin and Carolina, 1957 (Box 317)
    - Interstate, 1957 (Box 317)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1957 (Box 317)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1957 (Box 317)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1957 (Box 317)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1957 (Box 317)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1957 (Box 317)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1957 (Box 318)
    - Pennyslvania, 1957 (Box 318)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1957 (Box 318)
    - Rinchmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1957 (Box 318)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1957 (Box 318)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1957 (Box 318)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1957 (Box 318)
    - Southern, 1957 (Box 318)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1957 (Box 319)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1957 (Box 319)
    - Virginia Central, 1957 (Box 319)
    - Virginian, 1957 (Box 319)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1957 (Box 319)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1957 (Box 319)
    - Winchester and Western, 1957 (Box 319)
  - 1958.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1958 (Box 319)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1958 (Box 319)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1958 (Box 319)
    - Carolina and Northwestern, 1958 (Box 319)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1958 (Box 320)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1958 (Box 320)
    - Clinchfield, 1958 (Box 320)
    - Danville and Western, 1958 (Box 320)
    - Franklin and Carolina, 1958 (Box 320)
    - Interstate, 1958 (Box 320)
    - Louisville, 1958 (Box 320)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1958 (Box 320)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1958 (Box 320)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1958 (Box 321)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1958 (Box 321)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1958 (Box 321)
    - Pennsylvania, 1958 (Box 321)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1958 (Box 321)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1958 (Box 321)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1958 (Box 322)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1958 (Box 322)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1958 (Box 322)
    - Southern, 1958 (Box 322)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1958 (Box 322)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1958 (Box 322)
    - Virginia Central, 1958 (Box 322)
    - Virginian, 1958 (Box 322)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1958 (Box 322)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1958 (Box 322)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1958 (Box 322)
    - Winchester and Western, 1958 (Box 322)
  - 1959.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1959 (Box 323)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1959 (Box 323)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1959 (Box 323)
    - Carolina and Northwestern, 1959 (Box 323)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1959 (Box 323)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1959 (Box 323)
    - Clinchfield, 1959 (Box 323)
    - Danville and Western, 1959 (Box 323)
    - Interstate, 1959 (Box 324)
    - Louisville, 1959 (Box 324)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1959 (Box 324)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1959 (Box 324)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1959 (Box 324)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1959 (Box 324)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1959 (Box 324)
    - Pennsylvania, 1959 (Box 324)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated, 1959 (Box 324)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated, 1959 (Box 325)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1959 (Box 325)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1959 (Box 325)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1959 (Box 325)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1959 (Box 325)
    - Southern, 1959 (Box 325)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1959 (Box 325)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1959 (Box 325)
    - Virginia Central, 1959 (Box 325)
    - Virginian, 1959 (Box 326)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1959 (Box 326)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1959 (Box 326)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1959 (Box 326)
    - Winchester and Western, 1959 (Box 326)
  - 1960.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1960 (Box 326)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1960 (Box 326)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1960 (Box 326)
    - Carolina and Northwestern, 1960 (Box 326)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1960 (Box 326)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1960 (Box 326)
    - Clinchfield, 1960 (Box 327)
    - Danville and Western, 1960 (Box 327)
    - Interstate, 1960 (Box 327)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1960 (Box 327)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1960 (Box 327)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1960 (Box 327)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1960 (Box 327)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1960 (Box 327)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1960 (Box 327)
    - Pennsylvania, 1960 (Box 328)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1960 (Box 328)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1960 (Box 328)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1960 (Box 328)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1960 (Box 328)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1960 (Box 328)
    - Southern, 1960 (Box 328)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1960 (Box 328)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1960 (Box 329)
    - Virginia Central, 1960 (Box 329)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1960 (Box 329)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1960 (Box 329)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1960 (Box 329)
    - Winchester and Western, 1960 (Box 329)
  - 1961.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1961 (Box 329)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1961 (Box 329)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1961 (Box 329)
    - Carolina and Northwestern, 1961 (Box 329)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1961 (Box 329)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1961 (Box 329)
    - Clinchfield, 1961 (Box 329)
    - Danville and Western, 1961 (Box 330)
    - Interstate, 1961 (Box 330)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1961 (Box 330)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1961 (Box 330)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1961 (Box 330)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1961 (Box 330)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1961 (Box 330)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1961 (Box 330)
    - Pennsylvania, 1961 (Box 330)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated, 1961 (Box 330)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated, 1961 (Box 331)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1961 (Box 331)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1961 (Box 331)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1961 (Box 331)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1961 (Box 331)
    - Southern, 1961 (Box 331)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1961 (Box 331)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1961 (Box 331)
    - Virginia Central, 1961 (Box 331)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1961 (Box 332)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1961 (Box 332)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1961 (Box 332)
    - Winchester and Western, 1961 (Box 332)
  - 1962.
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1962 (Box 332)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1962 (Box 332)
    - Carolina and Northwestern, 1962 (Box 332)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1962 (Box 332)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1962 (Box 332)
    - Clinchfield, 1962 (Box 332)
    - Danville and Western, 1962 (Box 333)
    - Interstate, 1962 (Box 333)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1962 (Box 333)
    - Norfolk, Franklin, and Danville, 1962 (Box 333)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1962 (Box 333)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1962 (Box 333)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1962 (Box 333)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1962 (Box 333)
    - Pennsylvania, 1962 (Box 333)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1962 (Box 334)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1962 (Box 334)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1962 (Box 334)
    - Rosslyn Crossing, 1962 (Box 334)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1962 (Box 334)
    - Southern, 1962 (Box 334)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1962 (Box 334)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1962 (Box 334)
    - Virginia Central, 1962 (Box 335)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1962 (Box 335)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1962 (Box 335)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1962 (Box 335)
    - Winchester and Western, 1962 (Box 335)
  - 1963.
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1963 (Box 335)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1963 (Box 335)
    - Carolina and Northwestern, 1963 (Box 335)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1963 (Box 335)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1963 (Box 335)
    - Clinchfield, 1963 (Box 335)
    - Danville and Western, 1963 (Box 336)
    - Interstate, 1963 (Box 336)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1963 (Box 336)
    - Norfolk, Franklin, and Danville, 1963 (Box 336)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1963 (Box 336)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1963 (Box 336)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1963 (Box 336)
    - Pennsylvania, 1963 (Box 336)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated, 1963 (Box 336)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated, 1963 (Box 337)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1963 (Box 337)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1963 (Box 337)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1963 (Box 337)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1963 (Box 337)
    - Southern, 1963 (Box 337)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1963 (Box 337)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1963 (Box 337)
    - Virginia Central, 1963 (Box 337)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1963 (Box 337)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1963 (Box 337)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1963 (Box 338)
    - Winchester and Western, 1963 (Box 338)
  - 1964.
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1964 (Box 338)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1964 (Box 338)
    - Carolina and Northwestern, 1964 (Box 338)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1964 (Box 338)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1964 (Box 338)
    - Clinchfield, 1964 (Box 338)
    - Danville and Western, 1964 (Box 338)
    - Interstate, 1964 (Box 338)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1964 (Box 339)
    - Norfolk, Franklin, and Danville, 1964 (Box 339)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1964 (Box 339)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1964 (Box 339)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1964 (Box 339)
    - Pennsylvania, 1964 (Box 339)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1964 (Box 339)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1964 (Box 339)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1964 (Box 340)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1964 (Box 340)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1964 (Box 340)
    - Southern, 1964 (Box 340)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1964 (Box 340)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1964 (Box 340)
    - Virginia Central, 1964 (Box 340)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1964 (Box 340)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1964 (Box 340)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1964 (Box 340)
    - Winchester and Western, 1964 (Box 340)
  - 1965.
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1965 (Box 341)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1965 (Box 341)
    - Carolina and Northwestern, 1965 (Box 341)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1965 (Box 341)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1965 (Box 341)
    - Clinchfield, 1965 (Box 341)
    - Danville and Western, 1965 (Box 341)
    - Interstate, 1965 (Box 341)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1965 (Box 342)
    - Norfolk, Franklin, and Danville, 1965 (Box 342)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1965 (Box 342)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1965 (Box 342)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1965 (Box 342)
    - Pennsylvania, 1965 (Box 342)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1965 (Box 342)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1965 (Box 342)
    - Richmond Terminal Railway, 1965 (Box 343)
    - Rossyln Connecting, 1965 (Box 343)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1965 (Box 343)
    - Southern, 1965 (Box 343)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1965 (Box 343)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1965 (Box 343)
    - Virginia Central, 1965 (Box 343)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1965 (Box 343)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1965 (Box 343)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1965 (Box 343)
    - Winchester and Western, 1965 (Box 343)
  - 1966.
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1966 (Box 344)